(Sheldon:)...is because I have to attend a memorial
service for Professor Tupperman.
- That sounds like a long and tedious evening.
- Ah, it will be.
(Sheldon:)Honestly, if I must endure
a long and tedious evening...
(Sheldon:)...I'd rather it be with you on date night.
(Sheldon:)But I have no choice.
The tenure committee is going to be there.
(Amy:)Oh, well, in that case,
perhaps I should come along.
(Sheldon:)Now that I think about it,
that would be helpful.
(Amy:)Of course it would.
I'm well versed in academic politics,
and as a respected scientist...
(Amy:)...I can only raise your stock
as a candidate.
(Sheldon:)Actually, I meant you could drive me.
(Sheldon:)But if it makes you happy,
that other stuff too.
- Do anything interesting today?
- Not really. I was out shopping with Amy.
(Penny:)She wanted me to help her find something
for this memorial.
What, Sheldon's going to be there?
We all promised we weren't gonna go.
- Oh. What ajerk.
- I know.
(Leonard:)I was hoping to go
without anyone finding out.